hi I'm Ranger Enzo
I'm a full time work from home mom I'm
mama - and Vaughn is 12 years old and
Jessie for six years of wood I am an
outreach manager for a European firm
I run the digital marketing agency with
a partner I am a contributing writer and
editor for one of the soft broadsheets
here in the Philippines and I also run a
two-year-old on Instagram shop I've been
working from home for almost eight years
now I decided to I decided to be a wfh
because I wanted to spend more time with
my family but at the same time
professionally I wanted to be successful
in in my chosen field and working from
home allowed me to do that aside from
working from home during the during this
time of bcq I was also able to do
volunteer work for this group which
would be nice helping Benoist
basically we're a group of around 7 to 8
professionals who volunteer like a few
hours every day to help people who have
been affected by the urban environment
so these are these are laborers these
are housewives these are senior citizens
who suddenly couldn't earn their wage
and whose budget everyday has been
affected because their their company
since working they couldn't find any
work which is understandable so what we
do is that we accommodate messages that
come in in our group and then we we try
to do background checks we try to
interview them we try to get some
important documents to show that these
are people who really need help and then
we try to connect them with a donor with
a benefactor who can provide groceries
who can provide medicines for the family
that will last a month
it's a life-changing experience because
I was exposed to different problems of
society and I was able to meet other
people and understand that how the
pandemic is actually affecting their
lives and it's it's life-changing as
well to know that even with something as
simple as doing Facebook we were able to
help other people who were able to help
ease the burden that they are feeling
because
it's also a good way to introduce
my children you know charity work and we
let them know that it's part of their
responsibilities as few months you know
if you couldn't do something just as
simple as connecting them to someone who
could help them it's I feel that this is
something that they can carry on even
when they're all grown ups already
[Music]